<Content>
  <FrontPage>
    <Quote><![CDATA[To distinguish the real from the unreal, one must experience them both.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Reality and I had a fundamental differing of opinions.  We're currently undergoing trial separation.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Intelligence tests are biased toward the literate.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Sanity is the playground for the unimaginative.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[History is written by those in power to justify the present. Memory is the same thing on a smaller scale.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[How we all would run in fear if only we could see inside our own twisted minds.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[We're all mad here. I'm mad. You're mad. "How do you know I'm mad?" said Alice. "You must be," said the Cat, "or you wouldn't have come here."]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Life is like a box of Malkavians, you never know what you're gonna get...]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[That's the worst thing about Malkavians...you never know whether to shoot them or listen to them. They'll either lead you right to your goal or try to get you to go sunbathing. Wouldn't surprise me if God was a Malkavian.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Be wary when you find yourself walking down a path towards knowledge--all such roads inevitably lead to madness.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Police don't have any suspects at this time, but they're pretty sure that it was you.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[What all suede kittens do... on hands and knees, you lap up the milk of me... and we purr, kitten, like dragonflies buzzing around frog bellies. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Real terror is not the sight of death, it is the fear of death. What is the fear of death? Terror of the unknown. Is it these eyes you peer into? No, I am not the unknown. You and I are closer kin than you think it were. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I can tell you and I are going to get along just like fire hoses. When we get turned on, there's bound to be flames! ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Every time I yank a jawbone from a skull and ram it into an eyesocket, I know I'm building a better future. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Oooh, what do we have here? Another scrumptious young plaything straight out of life and into my club? Mmm... you smell new, little boy, like fabric softener dew on freshly mowed Astroturf. Oh, I'm not frightening you, am I, duckling? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The Sabbat are worthless, man. Fake tits on a zombie worthless. Fun to watch though. Like the Three Stooges with chainsaws. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Whoever fights monsters should see to it that in the process he does not become a monster. and when you look into an abyss, the abyss also looks into you.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Gaze into the void. It is the perpetuity in which they dwell.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[This is a mean existence. Stay out of trouble]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You look familiar. Were you ever on a milk carton? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Look at you, hacker: a pathetic creature of meat and bone, panting and sweating as you run through my corridors. How can you challenge a perfect, immortal machine? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[What is a drop of rain, compared to the storm? What is a thought, compared to the mind? Our unity is full of wonder which your tiny individualism cannot even conceive. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The Polito form is dead, insect. Are you afraid? What is it you fear? The end of your trivial existence? When the history of my glory is written, your species shall only be a footnote to my magnificence. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You move like an insect. You think like an insect. You ARE an insect. There is another who can serve my purpose. Take care not to fall too far out of my favor... patience is not characteristic of a goddess. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Remember, it is my will that guided you here. It is my will that gave you your cybernetic implants, the only beauty in that meat you call a body. If you value that meat... you will do as I tell you. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You travel within the glory of my memories, insect. I can feel your fear as you tread the endless expanse of my mind. Make yourself comfortable... before long I will decorate my home with your carcass. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Better to die fighting for freedom then be a prisoner all the days of your life.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Didn't we have some fun though? Remember when the platform was sliding into the fire pit and I said 'Goodbye' and you were like 'NO WAY!' and then I was all 'We pretended we were going to murder you'? That was great.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[That's the second biggest monkey head I've ever seen]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Hey dudes, thanks for rescuing me! Let's go for a burger...Ha! Ha! Ha!]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[War. War never changes.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Thank you for visiting. But our princess is in another castle.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Most actions do not aim at anybodys defeat or loss. They aim at an improvement in conditions.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[My strength is not in steel and fire, that is what the parasites will never understand. A season for all things! A time to live and a time to die, a time to build... and a time to destroy! ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I remember when me and the Kraut put you on that sub. You were no more than two. You were my ace in the hole. But you were also the closest thing I've ever had to a son. That's why this hurts, kid. Life isn't strictly business. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You know nothing, Jon Snow.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I came to this place to build the impossible. You came to rob what you could never build - a Hun gaping at the gates of Rome. Even the air you breathe is sponged from my account. Well... breathe deep, so later you might remember the taste. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[All rational action is in the first place individual action. Only the individual thinks. Only the individual reasons. Only the individual acts.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[We all make choices in life, but in the end our choices make us.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Ah, that's better. Atlas, Ryan, Atlas, Ryan, duh duh duh, duh duh duh. Time was you could get something decent on the radio. The artist has a duty to seduce the ear and delight the spirit, so say goodbye to those two blowhards, and hello to an evening with Sander Cohen!]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Ohhhh, I can smell the malt vinegar in this one. I've waited so long for something tasty to come to this little burg, but all that pass are yokels and rubes. Where are my manners? Come in, come in! Sander Cohen awaits you, at the Fleet Hall!]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The beginning of wisdom is the statement 'I do not know.' The person who cannot make that statement is one who will never learn anything. And I have prided myself on my ability to learn.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[That ain't no dog. It's a Zergling, Lester. Smaller attack Zerg. They shouldn't be out this far unless...]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Remember us, Executor. Remember what was done here today. And may Adun watch over you. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[All government wars are unjust.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Awaken my child, and embrace the glory that is your birthright. Know that I am the Overmind; the eternal will of the Swarm, and that you have been created to serve me. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Full government control of all activities of the individual is virtually the goal of both national parties.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[So you see, my friends; we fight not only to save Aiur, but all creation. If we fall to the Zerg then the Overmind will run rampant among the stars, consuming all sentience, all life. It is up to us to put an end to this madness, once and for all. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[My children, the hour of our victory is at hand. For upon this world of Aiur shall we incorporate the strongest known species into our fold. Then shall we be the greatest of creation's children. We shall be... Perfect. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[For the End of the World spell, press control, alt, delete. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[What we do in death, echoes in eternity]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Side effects may include: dry mouth, nausea, vomiting, water retention, painful rectal itch, hallucination, dementia, psychosis, coma, death, and halitosis. Magic is not for everyone. Consult your doctor before use ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The boy believed you could be saved, but he didn't know what burns within your soul. When in your heart, you know we are the same.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[My blood cries out for the vengeance of my people's blood, which can only be repaid with at least twice as much blood! Or maybe THREE times as much blood! Like if you went to hell, and it was full of blood, and that blood was on fire, and it was raining blood, then maybe THAT would be enough blood! Eh... but probably not.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Join us, brothers and sisters. Join us in the shadows where we stand vigilant. Join us as we carry the duty that cannot be forsworn. And should you perish, know that your sacrifice will not be forgotten... and that one day, we shall join you. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Why is it whenever someone says "with all due respect", they really mean "kiss my ass"? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You think I'm crazy, don't you? Sometimes crazy is the best way to go. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[We have no beginning. We have no end. We are infinite. Millions of years after your civilization has been eradicated and forgotten, we will endure. We are eternal. The pinnacle of evolution and existence. Before us, you are nothing. Your extinction is inevitable. We are the end of everything. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[How can you fight your own people? <br>Anyone who fights us is either stupid or on Saren's payroll. Killing the latter is business. Killing the former is a favour to the universe. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Shepard. Wrex.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You must have family other than your father. Don't you miss them? <br> You trying to make me cry, Shepard? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I thought you were a hero! Hero's don't do things like this! I wish I'd never met you. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Shepard, you're making a habit of costing me more than time and money.<br>I'm sorry, I'm having trouble hearing you- I'm getting a lot of bullshit on this line. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Put more of the stuff in the... the thing more stuff goes in. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Argh! You want me to go crawling through the ducts again.<br><i>I enjoy the sight of humans on their knees.</i><br><i>That is a joke.</i><br>Right. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Ah yes, "Reapers". The immortal race of sentient starships allegedly waiting in dark space. We have dismissed that claim. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Turns out, mess with someone's head enough, you can turn a scared little kid into an all powerful bitch. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I have ruled out the possibility of an artificially intelligent virus, unless it's *very* intelligent... and is toying with me. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Human, you've changed nothing. Your species has the attention of those infinitely your greater. That which you know as Reapers are your salvation through destruction. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[We do not comprehend the organic fascination of self-poisoning, auditory damage and sexually transmitted disease. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I'll relinquish one bullet. Where do you want it? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Government is not reason, it is not eloquence – it is force. Like fire, it is a dangerous servant and fearful master.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Man thinks not only for the sake of thinking, but also in order to act.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The President has been kidnapped by ninjas. Are you a bad enough dude to rescue the president?]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Never pay more than 20 bucks for a computer game.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[WELCOME TO WARP ZONE!]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[It's time to kick ass and chew bubble gum...and I'm all out of gum]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[It's dangerous to go alone! Take this.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[When due process fails us, we really do live in a world of terror]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Amazing when you think about it. All the hours I dreamed of working here. All the heroic fantasies when really this place is just a cinderblock bunker with a carpet]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Human beings may not be perfect, but a computer program with language synthesis is hardly the answer to the world's problems.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Every war is the result of a difference of opinion. Maybe the biggest questions can only be answered by the greatest of conflicts]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[When the people fear the government, there is tyranny. When the government fears the people, there is liberty.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Ever wonder why big car corporations pay two percent tax and the guys on the assembly line pay forty?]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Corporations are so big, you don't even know who you're working for. That's terror. Terror built into the system.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Do you ever ask what it's all for? The surveillance, the police, the shoot-on-sight laws? Is that freedom?]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You will be who you will be. We are our choices. And we can choose to lead humanity away from this... darkness.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The checks and balances of democratic governments were invented because humans themselves realized how unfit they were to govern themselves. They needed a system, yes. An industrial age machine.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The human being created civilization not because of willingness but of a need to be assimilated into higher orders of structure and meaning.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The basic human need to be watched was once satisfied by God. Now, the same functionality can be replicated with data-mining algorithms.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The unplanned organism is a question asked by Nature and answered by Death.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The individual desires judgment. Without that desire, the cohesion of groups is impossible, and so is civilization.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The cake is a lie.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when my fear is gone I will turn and face fear's path, and only I will remain. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[He who controls the spice, controls the universe.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Either you have an enviable memory, or a pitiable life, to know nothing of regret.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I like swords, I follow orders; there's nothing else to know about me.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[No one has a place here. Your farmers wish to be merchants. The merchants dream of being nobles, and the nobles become warriors. No one is content to be who they are.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Happiness is fragile. Nothing can be built upon it that will last. Only duty endures.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Nothing is more difficult, and therefore more precious, than to be able to decide.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Disobedience is the true foundation of liberty. The obedient must be slaves.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Fuck off with your sofa units and string green stripe patterns, I say never be complete, I say stop being perfect, I say let... lets evolve, let the chips fall where they may. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Tomorrow will be the most beautiful day of Raymond K. Hessel's life. His breakfast will taste better than any meal you and I have ever tasted. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[People do it everyday, they talk to themselves... they see themselves as they'd like to be, they don't have the courage you have, to just run with it. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I'm not some old man! Or a wounded prisoner! Motherfucker... Don't you dare touch the girl. You won't be the first pig I've gutted! ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[When the people fear the government there is tyranny, when the government fears the people there is liberty. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[God Damn! We just had a near-life experience, fellas. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[His name is Robert Paulson. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[We are Sex Bob-Omb and we are here to make you think about death and get sad and stuff. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I'm in lesbians with you. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[You want to know the best thing about Z-land? No- no Facebook status updates. You know, Rob Curtis is gearing up for Friday. Who cares? ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Me? I've had so many names. Old names that only the wind and the trees can pronounce. I am the mountain, the forest and the earth. I am... I am a faun. Your most humble servant, Your Highness. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The moon will be full in three days. Your spirit shall forever remain among the humans. You shall age like them, you shall die like them, and all memory of you shall fade in time. And we'll vanish along with it. You will never see us again. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Stop right there, criminal scum!]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Sky People can not learn, they do not see. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Those who deny freedom to others deserve it not for themselves.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I know now why you cry. But it's something I can never do. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The answer is out there, Neo, and it's looking for you, and it will find you if you want it to. ]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[I'm trying to free your mind, Neo. But I can only show you the door. You're the one that has to walk through it.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Can it wait for a bit? I'm in the middle of some calibrations.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Heh heh... hm, hm, mmm, hngh, hee hee hee A HA HA HA HA HA HAAA! HO HO HO HOo. AH! AH! Ha... hoo... ho... haa... Oh, oh oh, ha... What were we laughing about?]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[It is easy to be conspicuously 'compassionate' if others are being forced to pay the cost.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Men are fighting... because they are convinced that the extermination of adversaries is the only means of promoting their own well-being.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Sovereignty must not be used for inflicting harm on anyone, whether citizen or foreigner.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[If history could teach us anything, it would be that private property is inextricably linked with civilization.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[The nonhuman animals never proceed beyond instinctive urges and conditioned reflexes.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[There can be no freedom in art and literature where the government determines who shall create them.]]></Quote>
    <Quote><![CDATA[Capitalism gave the world what it needed, a higher standard of living for a steadily increasing number of people.]]></Quote>
  </FrontPage>
  <FeaturedProject>
    <FLVThumbnail link="http://www.youtube.com/user/LoveLifeAndAnarchy"><![CDATA[works/featured/lla.flv]]></FLVThumbnail>
    <FLVBackgroud><![CDATA[works/featured/websitebg.flv]]></FLVBackgroud>
  </FeaturedProject>
  <AboutPage>
    <About flv="works/flv/about.flv"><![CDATA[Evokelabs was founded in Sydney Australia by interactive designer/developer Adrian Pikios. Since 2004, Adrian has maintained an interactive driven studio helping people all over the world achieve their creative multimedia goals. Attracting the attention of clients and agencies for being efficient, knowledgeable and affordable, Adrian hopes to help small to medium businesses as well as major global agencies build a better digital world.Our services include interactive design, interactive development, HTML5, CSS, javascript, 3d production, flash design, actionscript, banner design and coding, web games, wordpress, cms, ecommerce, motion design, video production and eDMs.]]></About>
  </AboutPage>
  <ForwardTitle>
    <label><![CDATA[Yep]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Let's see this]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Looks interesting]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I would like to know more]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Show me]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Launch]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Ok, you have a go]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Go]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[How do they work?]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[What is this?]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I'm curious]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[This better be good]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[This better be worth it]]></label>
  </ForwardTitle>
  <BackTitle>
    <label><![CDATA[Not interested in this]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[TL:DR take me back]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[This wasn't the droid]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I liked how it was before]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I should go]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I am no longer here]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Back]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Not today]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Previous]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[I've seen enough]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Nah]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[Nope]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[No chance]]></label>
    <label><![CDATA[No way]]></label>
  </BackTitle>
  <Music>
    <piece><![CDATA[_insertedAssets/sounds/track1.mp3]]></piece>
  </Music>
</Content>